http://www.coho.net/privacy_policy.php

Privacy Policy
Coho's Privacy Policy for your Protection.
Privacy Policy
This privacy statement applies to the website of:
Whiz to Coho, Inc.
support@whiz.to
We respect your privacy. This is why we have taken the time to disclose our information collection practices and our privacy policy. Please take the time to review this document.
Collecting information provides specific benefits to our website visitors:
Collecting your information allows you to manage your account online.
We collect information for the following purpose(s):
• Completing or supporting an activity
• Website and system administration
• Research and development
• Tailoring the website for its visitors
• Research, analysis, reporting
• Build records of individual visitors
• Contacting our visitors (except via telephone) for promotion of the site or products
• Contacting our visitors via telephone for promotion of the site or products
• other-purpose
Who has access to the information we collect?
• Ourselves
Of the information we do collect, we allow our visitors the following access to the information:
Access is given to other collected information. (For example, users can access things such as their online account charges).
If you believe that our website has collected incorrect information or if you would like to dispute any information, please contact us using the address at the top of this page.
Get in touch
Whiz To Coho, Inc.12800 NW Bishop RdHillsboro, OR 97124, USA
Phone:
(503) 647-5957
Fax:
(503) 214-5490
Email: support@coho.net
CCB # 165990
Follow us
Follow us on Facebook or contact us via email, so you can be informed every time
we do something.
